Miracle.
You step up, swing it on the first green Drive straight down like a laser beam Confidence drive they've never seen But I know how this will go Balls in the bunker on hole three Still you smile like it's old routine You line it up, you play it clean Never cheat or let it roll Straight shooter who can't shoot straight You never lie, never hesitate
Chocolate strokes put you on your feet You're teeing up but you won't escape I watch the score climb with the sun We're way past par but having fun Hit the water, you never run It's a Benji Brownie where Fork, put, freeze and rump that bite Still you laugh through every slice The mic is no secret, right?
Miles to a fault, I swear.
Straight shooter who can't shoot straight.
You never won, never hesitate.
You tee it up, but you won't escape.
Could have keeped it out, but that's not you.
Counting every swing, you'll matter true or screwed.
Your scorecard looks like modern art, but you play around with an honest heart.
Straight shooter who can't shoot straight.
You never won, never hesitate.
Chalk and strokes, but you won your fate.
You tee it up, but you won't escape.
Still so you're proud to go every all A legend with a bulgy soul Can't shoot straight but it makes you all Can't shoot straight but it makes you all